(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Victoria and Linda are sisters.
Their parents make them wash dishes.
They take turns.
Victoria washes the dishes on Monday, Wednesday, and
Friday.
Linda washes the dishes on Tuesday, Thursday, and
Saturday.
On Sunday, they flip a coin.
Today, it was Victoria's turn to wash dishes.
Linda took advantage of this.
She used three dishes at dinner.
She had one dish for rice, one dish
for meat, and another dish for dessert.
Why do you have to make me wash
more?
Victoria yelled.
It's fair, Linda said.
Victoria never did that to Linda.
She planned to make Linda wash more dishes
tomorrow.